(Sheldon:)Intimacy in any form
has been challenging for me,
(Sheldon:)but I'd like to show her
how important she is,
(Sheldon:)and it feels like
now might be the right time.
(Penny:)Sheldon, that's
so beautiful.
(Sheldon:)Then it's settled.
(Sheldon:)Amy's birthday present
will be my genitals.
(Amy:)Thanks for taking me out.
(Penny:)Well, you're spending
your birthday with Sheldon.
(Penny:)Why not celebrate early?
(Bernadette:)So where do
you want to go?
(Amy:)I heard that new Mexican place
on Green Street is good.
(Penny:)Sure, sure. Or we could
take you to get a bikini wax.
(Amy:)Why would I get a bikini
wax for my birthday?
(Penny:)Uh, I don't know.
It was just a thought.
(Amy:)I think I'll just
stick to Mexican.
(Bernadette:)Great. And then maybe after,
we can watch a dirty movie,
(Bernadette:)and if anybody has any questions
about what happened or how,
(Bernadette:)we can answer them.
(Amy:)Okay, what
is going on?
(Penny:)Oh, we just want you
to be prepared